Secret Summer is a romance, family, comedy film directed by Rick Bota.
Appraiser Rachel (Lindsey Shaw) receives the news that her top-notched client wants to
buyout a small town’s beloved library to build a resort and spa on the land.
Rachel is completely against the idea of leaving NYC
but loses the argument to her boss.
So Rachel packs her bags and flies out to California.
During her first visit to the library she runs into writer, Jake (Derek Theler), who is
researching the tale of Captain Black Bart’s hidden treasures for his next novel.
With hopes of saving the library, Mrs.
Archer (Rachel Ticotin), the librarian, pushes Jake to show
Rachel what the library means to the town.
Jake’s already got a lot on his plate with his research and taking care of his niece, Hailey
(Chiara Aurelia), and nephew, Noah (Max Page), for the summer but he agrees to help out.
As Rachel learns what the library means to the community she
must find away to save it before it’s too late.
Rachel Turney, played by Lindsey Shaw.
Jake Kenman, played by Derek Theler.
Hailey, played by Chiara Aurelia.
Janice, played by Emily Rose.
Noah, played by Max Page.
Daniel Kenman, played by Lucas Bryant.
Secret Admirer is a 1985 American teen romantic comedy film co-written and directed by
David Greenwalt in his feature film directorial debut, and starring C.
Thomas Howell, Lori Loughlin, Kelly Preston and Fred Ward.
The original music score was composed by Jan Hammer.
The film was produced at the height of the teen sex
comedy cinema craze in the mid-1980s.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.